{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Network Technology",
    "Term": "Pre-finals",
    "Title": "05 Routing Fundamentals",
    "LastModified": "20 May 2024",
    "Authors": [
      ""
    ],
    "References": [
      "05 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the process wherein a new string of information is added to an existing unit to form a new unit of information?",
      "answer": "Encapsulation",
      "choices": [
        "Decapsulation",
        "Data payload",
        "Packet",
        "Encapsulation"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the reverse process of encapsulation wherein the header and tail of a packet are removed to obtain the data payload?",
      "answer": "Decapsulation",
      "choices": [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Data payload",
        "Packet",
        "Decapsulation"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be considered as the information to be transmitted?",
      "answer": "Data payload",
      "choices": [
        "Packet",
        "Header",
        "Tail",
        "Data payload"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a data unit that is exchanged and transmitted on a network?",
      "answer": "Packet",
      "choices": [
        "Header",
        "Data payload",
        "Tail",
        "Packet"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the information segment added before the data payload during packet assembly to facilitate information transmission?",
      "answer": "Header",
      "choices": [
        "Packet",
        "Data payload",
        "Tail",
        "Header"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the information segment added after the payload to facilitate information transmission?",
      "answer": "Tail",
      "choices": [
        "Packet",
        "Header",
        "Data payload",
        "Tail"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a specific block of information transferred over a network?",
      "answer": "Protocol Data Unit (PDU)",
      "choices": [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Decapsulation",
        "Internet Protocol (IP)",
        "Protocol Data Unit (PDU)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer transmits raw bits (1s or 0s) physically via the hardware?",
      "answer": "Physical layer",
      "choices": [
        "Data Link layer",
        "Network layer",
        "Transport layer",
        "Physical layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer exchanges a frame (or series of bits)?",
      "answer": "Data Link layer",
      "choices": [
        "Physical layer",
        "Network layer",
        "Transport layer",
        "Data Link layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer contains the source and destination address in a packet?",
      "answer": "Network layer",
      "choices": [
        "Physical layer",
        "Data Link layer",
        "Transport layer",
        "Network layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer includes a TCP header and data in a segment?",
      "answer": "Transport layer",
      "choices": [
        "Physical layer",
        "Data Link layer",
        "Network layer",
        "Transport layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer passes the data to the network connection?",
      "answer": "Session layer",
      "choices": [
        "Physical layer",
        "Data Link layer",
        "Network layer",
        "Session layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer formats the data for presentation?",
      "answer": "Presentation layer",
      "choices": [
        "Physical layer",
        "Data Link layer",
        "Network layer",
        "Presentation layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What layer receives or transmits the data by a software application?",
      "answer": "Application layer",
      "choices": [
        "Physical layer",
        "Data Link layer",
        "Network layer",
        "Application layer"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What protocol defines a packet and an addressing scheme?",
      "answer": "Internet Protocol (IP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
        "Internet Protocol (IP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What TCP/IP protocol handles errors and controls the process of sending data between computers?",
      "answer": "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol (IP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What TCP/IP protocol handles multicasting?",
      "answer": "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol (IP)",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What TCP/IP protocol obtains the physical address of a node from a specific IP number?",
      "answer": "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol (IP)",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What TCP/IP protocol allows a host with no local permanent data storage media to find its Internet address given its physical address?",
      "answer": "Reverse Address Resolution Protocol (RARP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol (IP)",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Reverse Address Resolution Protocol (RARP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to a family of LANs, covered by a group of IEEE 802.3 standards?",
      "answer": "Ethernet",
      "choices": [
        "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)",
        "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)",
        "Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM)",
        "Ethernet"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What protocol is used for data transfer across a serial line?",
      "answer": "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)",
      "choices": [
        "Ethernet",
        "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)",
        "Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM)",
        "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a set of ANSI protocols for sending digital data over fiber optic cable?",
      "answer": "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)",
      "choices": [
        "Ethernet",
        "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)",
        "Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM)",
        "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to a wide area protocol that features high data rates and equal-sized packets/cells suitable for text, audio, and video data transfer?",
      "answer": "Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM)",
      "choices": [
        "Ethernet",
        "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)",
        "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)",
        "Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a WAN protocol for LAN internetworking that provides a fast and efficient method of transmitting information from one user device to another across multiple switches and routers?",
      "answer": "Frame Relay",
      "choices": [
        "Ethernet",
        "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)",
        "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)",
        "Frame Relay"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What protocol is used when a network terminal needs to pass data from one segment to another without changing its current IP address information?",
      "answer": "Proxy ARP",
      "choices": [
        "Ethernet",
        "Point-to-Point Protocol (PPP)",
        "Fiber distributed data interface (FDDI)",
        "Proxy ARP"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What protocol transfers data between the Internet layer and network access layers?",
      "answer": "Internet Protocol (IP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
        "Internet Protocol (IP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What protocol routes packets to remote hosts?",
      "answer": "Internet Protocol (IP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
        "Internet Protocol (IP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What TCP/IP protocol also includes an echo request/reply \r\nthat is used to test whether a destination is reachable and responding?",
      "answer": "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol (IP)",
        "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP)",
        "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the basic element of data communication networks, which is the process of selecting paths on a network along which packets are sent from a source to a destination?",
      "answer": "Routing",
      "choices": [
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "routing device (Router)",
        "Routing"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What enables a router to compare the destination address to the available routes in its routing table and to select the best path?",
      "answer": "Path determination",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Routes",
        "routing device (Router)",
        "Path determination"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the path information used to guide packet forwarding?",
      "answer": "Routes",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "routing device (Router)",
        "Routes"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a network device that forwards packets to a destination subnet based on routes?",
      "answer": "routing device (Router)",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "routing device (Router)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the overall network-wide process of finding the most efficient path for forwarding the IP packet from source to destination?",
      "answer": "Packet routing",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Packet routing"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What select a proper path according to the destination address of a received IP packet and forward the packet to the next router?",
      "answer": "A gateway and an intermediate node (a router)",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "A gateway and an intermediate node (a router)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What identifies a destination subnet?",
      "answer": "Destination",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Destination"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What identifies a subnet together with a destination IP address?",
      "answer": "Mask",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Mask"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the interface through which a data packet is sent out of the local router?",
      "answer": "Outbound interface",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Outbound interface"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the _______ address used by the router to forward the data packet to the destination subnet?",
      "answer": "Next hop",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Next hop"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is simply a passing or moving of information between interfaces according to the “directions”?",
      "answer": "Packet Forwarding",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Packet Forwarding"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the way a packet is handled by the underlying physical networks under the control of the network layer?",
      "answer": "Packet Delivery",
      "choices": [
        "Routing",
        "Path determination",
        "Routes",
        "Packet Delivery"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when the IP node forwards a packet to its final destination in the network?",
      "answer": "Direct Delivery",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Hunger",
        "Indirect Hunger",
        "Indirect Delivery",
        "Direct Delivery"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when the IP node (host) forwards a packet to an intermediate node (IP router) because the final destination is not on a directly attached network?",
      "answer": "Indirect Delivery",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Routing",
        "Indirect Routiing",
        "Indirect Delivery",
        "Direct Delivery"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Network devices need to forward IP packets from different subnets to their destination IP subnets.",
      "answer": "The statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di ko na po malala, Your Honor.",
        "Di po ako nag review, Your Honor."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "A router discovers ______ using multiple methods in which it selects the optimal route and installs it in its IP routing table.",
      "answer": "Routes",
      "choices": [
        "Packets",
        "Bits",
        "Data",
        "Routes"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "A router forwards IP ______ based on routes in the IP routing table and manages path information by managing its IP routing table.",
      "answer": "Packets",
      "choices": [
        "Routes",
        "Packets",
        "Bits",
        "Data"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a database that contains information about which router network interface or port to place information to send it to a particular network segment?",
      "answer": "Routing Table (Huawei)",
      "choices": [
        "Destination/Mask",
        "Protocol (Proto)",
        "Preference (Pre)",
        "Routing Table (Huawei)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the destination network address and mask of a specific route?",
      "answer": "Destination/Mask",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table (Huawei)",
        "Protocol (Proto)",
        "Preference (Pre)",
        "Destination/Mask"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the protocol type of the route, that is, the protocol through which a router learns the route?",
      "answer": "Protocol (Proto)",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table (Huawei)",
        "Destination/Mask",
        "Preference (Pre)",
        "Protocol (Proto)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the routing protocol preference of the route?",
      "answer": "Preference (Pre)",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table (Huawei)",
        "Destination/Mask",
        "Protocol (Proto)",
        "Preference (Pre)"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the cost of the route?",
      "answer": "Cost",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table (Huawei)",
        "Destination/Mask",
        "Protocol (Proto)",
        "Cost"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the local router’s _____ address of the route to the destination network?",
      "answer": "Next Hop",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table (Huawei)",
        "Destination/Mask",
        "Protocol (Proto)",
        "Next Hop"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What indicates the outbound interface of the route?",
      "answer": "Interface",
      "choices": [
        "Routing Table (Huawei)",
        "Destination/Mask",
        "Protocol (Proto)",
        "Interface"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What command is used to check the IP routing table?",
      "answer": "display ip routing-table",
      "choices": [
        "display ip routing-table",
        "display ip address routing-table",
        "run display ip address routing-table",
        "run display ip routing-table"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What discovers two routes to 10.0.0.0/30, one is an OSPF route and the other is a static route, and compares the preferences of the two routes and selects the route with the lowest preference value?",
      "answer": "RTA",
      "choices": [
        "RTA",
        "TCP",
        "PDU",
        "OSI"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are automatically generated by devices and point to local directly connected networks?",
      "answer": "Direct routes",
      "choices": [
        "Direct routes",
        "Indirect Routiing",
        "Static routes",
        "Dynamic route"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are manually configured by network administrators and can be an effective method for networks with small and simple structures?",
      "answer": "Static routes",
      "choices": [
        "Static routes",
        "Indirect Routiing",
        "Direct routes",
        "Dynamic route"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are learned by dynamic routing protocols running on routers and use routing protocols to talk to other routers and find out what networks they are attached to?",
      "answer": "Dynamic route",
      "choices": [
        "Dynamic route",
        "Indirect Routiing",
        "Direct routes",
        "Static routes"
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The process of identifying the optimal route is the same for both routers and computers.",
      "answer": "The statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di ko na po malala, Your Honor.",
        "Di po ako nag review, Your Honor."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The router prefers the route with the highest preference value.",
      "answer": "The statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di ko na po malala, Your Honor.",
        "Di to kasama sa nireview ko."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The smaller the preference value, the higher the preference.",
      "answer": "The statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di po ako nag review, Your Honor.",
        "Pass. Di to kasama sa nireview ko."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The router selects the optimal route for the assigned IP with the lowest preference among all routes.",
      "answer": "The statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di ko na po malala, Your Honor.",
        "Babawi nalang po ako sa finals."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The assigned IP has the same destination/mask generated from different information sources.",
      "answer": "The statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di po ako nag review, Your Honor.",
        "Pass. Di to kasama sa nireview ko."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The other routes appear in the IP routing table.",
      "answer": "The statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Sometimes, its okay to Lets Go.",
        "Pass. Di to kasama sa nireview ko."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Routes generated from different information sources have the same default preference values.",
      "answer": "The statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Di po ako nag review, Your Honor.",
        "Babawi nalang po ako sa finals."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The default preference values may differ between devices of different vendors.",
      "answer": "The statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "The statement is TRUE .",
        "The statement is FALSE .",
        "Pero bakit parang kasalanan ko?",
        "Pass. Di to kasama sa nireview ko."
      ],
      "reference": "Routing Fundamentals",
      "term": "Pre-Finals"
    }
  ]
}
